Guide to the American Song Sheets Collection, circa 1830s-1920s, bulk 1850s-1880s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- American Song Sheets, circa 1850s-1880s, (4 boxes, items 1-1608)
  - Love Thee? (Box 2, Item 938)
  - Love Thee? (Box 2, Item 939)
  - Mother Would Comfort Me (Box 2, Item 940)
  - He's Gone to the Arms of Abraham (Box 2, Item 941)
  - How Are You Green-Backs? (Box 2, Item 942)
  - Larry Magee's Wedding (Box 2, Item 943)
  - When the Boys Come Home (Box 2, Item 944)
  - Her Bright Smiles Haunt Me Still (Box 2, Item 945)
  - Somebody's Courting Somebody (Box 2, Item 946)
  - I'd Choose to be a Baby (Box 2, Item 947)
  - Call Me Not Back from the Echoless Shore (Box 2, Item 948)
  - The Female Auctioneer (Box 2, Item 949)
  - Nellie of the North (Box 2, Item 950)
  - I'd Choose to be a Daisy (Box 2, Item 951)
  - Love Thee? (Box 2, Item 952)
  - Near the Banks of the Lone River (Box 2, Item 953)
  - Oh, Take Me to Thy Heart Again (Box 2, Item 954)
  - The Last of Summer (Box 2, Item 955)
  - Pretty Sally (Box 2, Item 956)
  - Traitor, Spare that Flag (Box 2, Item 957)
  - Rock Me to Sleep Mother (Box 2, Item 958)
  - Johnny, Fill Up the Bowl! (Box 2, Item 959)
  - Columbia, the Home of the World (Box 2, Item 960)
  - General Grant's Boys (Box 2, Item 961)
  - A Hundred Years Hence (Box 2, Item 962)
  - The Drummer of Antietam (Box 2, Item 963)
  - U.S. Grant the Hero of Appomatox (PICTURE) (Box 2, Item 964)
  - General Grant's Boys (Box 2, Item 965)
  - A Home Without A Mother (Box 2, Item 966)
  - My Loved One (Box 2, Item 967)
  - Tramp! Tramp! Tramp! The Prisoner's Hope (Box 2, Item 968)
  - Tramp! Tramp! Tramp! The Prisoner's Hope (Box 2, Item 969)
  - The Volunteer (Box 2, Item 970)
  - Let Me Kiss Him for His Mother (Box 2, Item 971)
  - Marching Along No. 2 (Box 2, Item 972)
  - Give Us Back Our Old Commander (Box 2, Item 973)
  - Flash Every Sabre Bright (Box 2, Item 974)
  - O, Carry Me Home (Box 2, Item 975)
  - My Sweet Wife, My Sallie (Box 2, Item 976)
  - Tramp! Tramp! Tramp! The Prisoner's Hope (Box 2, Item 977)
  - Tramp! Tramp! Tramp! The Prisoner's Hope (Box 2, Item 978)
  - Mother, I've Come Home to Die (Box 2, Item 979)
  - Taking Up Quarters (Box 2, Item 980)
  - Oh Jeff! Oh Jeff! How Are You Now? (Box 2, Item 981)
  - Who Will Care for Mother Now? (Box 2, Item 982)
  - Just After the Battle, Mother (Box 2, Item 983)
  - Tell Mother, I Die Happy (Box 2, Item 984)
  - The Dying Soldier to his Mother (Box 2, Item 985)
  - Want-A Substitute (Box 2, Item 986)
  - Kingdom Coming (Box 2, Item 987)
  - Brave Little Mac (Box 2, Item 988)
  - A Mother's Hymn in Time of War (Box 2, Item 989)
  - I Dreamed My Boy Was Home Again (Box 2, Item 990)
  - Tis Home Where the Heart Is (Box 2, Item 991)
  - Unfurl the Glorious Banner (Box 2, Item 992)
  - The Boys of Uncle Samu'l (Box 2, Item 993)
  - The Battle-Cry of Freedom (Box 2, Item 994)
  - Let the Rebels Put That in their Stripes (Box 2, Item 995)
  - Brave Boys (Box 2, Item 996)
  - Mother Kissed Me in My Dream (Box 2, Item 997)
  - Maryland, My Maryland! (Box 2, Item 998)
  - The Rebel Flags (Box 2, Item 999)
  - The Song of All Songs (Box 2, Item 1000)
  - Sherman's March to the Sea (Box 3, Item 1001)
  - Hail Columbia (Box 3, Item 1002)
  - Hail Columbia (Box 3, Item 1003)
  - Columbia's Hardy Seamen (Box 3, Item 1004)
  - Maryland, My Maryland! (Box 3, Item 1005)
  - The Banner of the Free (Box 3, Item 1006)
  - Mother, Dearest, I Am Coming (Box 3, Item 1007)
  - The Boys of Uncle Samu'l (Box 3, Item 1008)
  - Young Recruit (Box 3, Item 1009)
  - Brother, Tell Me of the Battle (Box 3, Item 1010)
  - Young Eph's Lament (Box 3, Item 1011)
  - Ye Sons of the North! (Box 3, Item 1012)
  - Grafted into the Army (Box 3, Item 1013)
  - Grafted into the Army (Box 3, Item 1014)
  - My Northern Boy to the War Has Gone! (Box 3, Item 1015)
  - Veteran Cavalry Song (Box 3, Item 1016)
  - When the Boys Come Home (Box 3, Item 1017)
  - When the Boys Come Home (Box 3, Item 1018)
  - Johnny, Fill Up the Bowl! (Box 3, Item 1019)
  - Dear Ones, I Am Coming Home! (Box 3, Item 1020)
  - Do They Think of Me at Home? (Box 3, Item 1021)
  - Willie We Have Missed You (Box 3, Item 1022)
  - Yes, I Would the War Were Over (Box 3, Item 1023)
  - The Army and Navy For Ever (Box 3, Item 1024)
  - The Union Marseillaise (Box 3, Item 1025)
  - Viva L'America (Box 3, Item 1026)
  - Viva L'America (Box 3, Item 1027)
  - Just Before the Battle, Mother (Box 3, Item 1028)
  - The Soldier's Funeral (Box 3, Item 1029)
  - Ellsworth's Avengers (Box 3, Item 1030)
  - The Volunteer (Box 3, Item 1031)
  - In Our Own Dear Homes Again! (Box 3, Item 1032)
  - The Tired Soldier (Box 3, Item 1033)
  - Mother, Dear, I'm Thinking of You (Box 3, Item 1034)
  - Willie'll Roam No Moer (Box 3, Item 1035)
  - Victory at Last (Box 3, Item 1036)
  - The Officer's Funeral (Box 3, Item 1037)
  - Will You Love Me Then as Now (Box 3, Item 1038)
  - What Irishmen Have Done (Box 3, Item 1039)
  - Abe Lincoln's Union Wagon (Box 3, Item 1040)
  - Oh Jeff! Oh Jeff! How Are You Now? (Box 3, Item 1041)
  - Our Battle-Flag (Box 3, Item 1042)
  - Volunteer's Song (Box 3, Item 1043)
  - The Contraband's Adventures (Box 3, Item 1044)
  - The Colored Volunteers (Box 3, Item 1045)
  - Yes, I Would the War Were Over (Box 3, Item 1046)
  - Who Will Care for Micky Now? (Box 3, Item 1047)
  - How Are You Green-backs? (Box 3, Item 1048)
  - Yanke Doodle (Box 3, Item 1049)
  - Grafted into the Army (Box 3, Item 1050)
  - On, On, On, the Boys Came Marching! (Box 3, Item 1051)
  - Mc'Clellan's Farewell to the Army of the Potomac (Box 3, Item 1052)
  - Victory at Last (Box 3, Item 1053)
  - A Yankee Man-of-War (Box 3, Item 1054)
  - Hail Columbia (Box 3, Item 1055)
  - Hail Columbia (Box 3, Item 1056)
  - Unfurl the Glorious Banner (Box 3, Item 1057)
  - Unfurl the Glorious Banner (Box 3, Item 1058)
  - Our Ulysses (Box 3, Item 1059)
  - Welcome Home (Box 3, Item 1060)
  - The Battle Cry of Freedom (Box 3, Item 1061)
  - Draw the Sword, Northland (Box 3, Item 1062)
  - Jeff Davis (Box 3, Item 1063)
  - Union Forever (Box 3, Item 1064)
  - The Housemaid (Box 3, Item 1065)
  - Darkey Conscript (Box 3, Item 1066)
  - The Banner of the Free (Box 3, Item 1067)
  - The Banner of the Free (Box 3, Item 1068)
  - The Battle-Cry of Freedom (Box 3, Item 1069)
  - The Battle-Cry of Freedom (Box 3, Item 1070)
  - Battle of Lookout Mountain (Box 3, Item 1071)
  - Better Times are Coming (Box 3, Item 1072)
  - The Boy Lay on the Battle-plain (Box 3, Item 1073)
  - Call Me Not Back from the Echoless Shore (Box 3, Item 1074)
  - The Captain of the Provost (Box 3, Item 1075)
  - The Captain With His Whiskers (Box 3, Item 1076)
  - Cavalry Song (Box 3, Item 1077)
  - The Colored Volunteers (Box 3, Item 1078)
  - Comin' from the War (Box 3, Item 1079)
  - Darling Little Sophie (Box 3, Item 1080)
  - Dear Mother, I've Come Home to Eat (Box 3, Item 1081)
  - Dear Ones, I Am Coming Home! (Box 3, Item 1082)
  - Draw the Sword, Northland (Box 3, Item 1083)
  - Drinking Song (Box 3, Item 1084)
  - The Drummer Boy's Farewell (Box 3, Item 1085)
  - The Dying Soldier (Box 3, Item 1086)
  - The Fall of Charleston! (Box 3, Item 1087)
  - The Female Auctioneer (Box 3, Item 1088)
  - The Flag of Our Union (Box 3, Item 1089)
  - The Flag of Our Union (Box 3, Item 1090)
  - Gay and Happy (Box 3, Item 1091)
  - The Following Beautiful Acrostio… (Box 3, Item 1092)
  - God Will Care for Mother Now (Box 3, Item 1093)
  - Hail, to the Nominee (Box 3, Item 1094)
  - He's Gone to the Arms of Abraham (Box 3, Item 1095)
  - Now Sheridan Whipped Longstreet (Box 3, Item 1096)
  - How Sherman's Veterans Took Atlanta (Box 3, Item 1097)
  - A Hundred Years Hence (Box 3, Item 1098)
  - Hurrah for the Flag of the Free (Box 3, Item 1099)
  - Hurrah for the Flag of the Free (Box 3, Item 1100)
  - I Remember the Hour When We Sadly Parted (Box 3, Item 1101)
  - I'm Going to Fight Mit Sigel (Box 3, Item 1102)
  - In Our Own Dear Homes Again! (Box 3, Item 1103)
  - Johnny, Fill Up Th Bowl (Box 3, Item 1104)
  - Just After the Battle, Mother (Box 3, Item 1105)
  - Just Before the Battle, Mother (Box 3, Item 1106)
  - Let Me Kiss Him for His Mother (Box 3, Item 1107)
  - Let the Rebels Put That in their Pipes (Box 3, Item 1108)
  - Marching Along No. 2 (Box 3, Item 1109)
  - Marching Along No. 2 (Box 3, Item 1110)
  - McClellan for President (Box 3, Item 1111)
  - McClellan Will Be President (Box 3, Item 1112)
  - Men and Knaves (Box 3, Item 1113)
  - The Message of Victory (Box 3, Item 1114)
  - Mother, Dearest, I Am Coming (Box 3, Item 1115)
  - Mother Kissed Me in My Dream (Box 3, Item 1116)
  - My Loved One (Box 3, Item 1117)
  - The Nation Mourns (Box 3, Item 1118)
  - My Northern Boy to the War Has Gone! (Box 3, Item 1119)
  - Nellie of the North (Box 3, Item 1120)
  - Parody on the Cottage by the Sea (Box 3, Item 1121)
  - Pretty Sally (Box 3, Item 1122)
  - A Soldier Is My Beau (Box 3, Item 1123)
  - The Song of All Songs (Box 3, Item 1124)
  - The Star Spangled Banner (Box 3, Item 1125)
  - Tell Mother, I Die Happy (Box 3, Item 1126)
  - That's What's the Matter No. 2 (Box 3, Item 1127)
  - Their Sham Shoulder-straps (Box 3, Item 1128)
  - Tis Home Where the Heart Is (Box 3, Item 1129)
  - To My Dearly Beloved (Box 3, Item 1130)
  - The Veteran's Song (Box 3, Item 1131)
  - The Veteran's Song (Box 3, Item 1132)
  - Victory at Last (Box 3, Item 1133)
  - Vir-gin-a (Box 3, Item 1134)
  - Vir-gin-a (Box 3, Item 1135)
  - Weep Not, Comrades, For Me (Box 3, Item 1136)
  - When Johnny Comes Marching Home (Box 3, Item 1137)
  - When This Cruel War Is Over (Box 3, Item 1138)
  - When This Cruel War Is Over (Box 3, Item 1139)
  - Who Will Care for Mother Now? (Box 3, Item 1140)
  - The Wife I Left Behind Me (Box 3, Item 1141)
  - Wife of My Bosom (Box 3, Item 1142)
  - Southern Wagon (Box 3, Item 1143)
  - The Star Spangled Banner (Box 3, Item 1144)
  - Flash Every Sabre Bright (Box 3, Item 1145)
  - I Dreamed My Boy Was Home Again (Box 3, Item 1146)
  - I Dreamed My Boy Was Home Again (Box 3, Item 1147)
  - At Penascola, General Bragg… (Box 3, Item 1148)
  - Original (Box 3, Item 1149)
  - No. 4 Campaign Song. O! What's the Matter (Box 3, Item 1150)
  - The Charming Young Widow I Met in the Train (Box 3, Item 1151)
  - A Contraband Song (Box 3, Item 1152)
  - Eight O'Clock in the Evening (Box 3, Item 1153)
  - The Electric Light (Box 3, Item 1154)
  - Every Day'l Be Sunday By and By (Box 3, Item 1155)
  - Ella Ree (Box 3, Item 1156)
  - Erin Go Bragh (Box 3, Item 1157)
  - Erin's Lovely Home (Box 3, Item 1158)
  - Every Day'l Be Sunday By and By (Box 3, Item 1159)
  - I Am Dreaming of the Loved Ones (Box 3, Item 1160)
  - Grave of Bonaparte (Box 3, Item 1161)
  - The Girl I Left Behind Me (Box 3, Item 1162)
  - I Love Music (Box 3, Item 1163)
  - I Vish I Vos de Mayor (Box 3, Item 1164)
  - I Whistle and Wait for Katie (Box 3, Item 1165)
  - I'd Rather Be a Rose (Box 3, Item 1166)
  - I'll Be All Smiles To-night (Box 3, Item 1167)
  - I'm a Dandy Mayor (Box 3, Item 1168)
  - I'm Proud I'm an Irishman's Son (Box 3, Item 1169)
  - I'm Going to Have My Name Above the Door (Box 3, Item 1170)
  - In de Morning by the Bright Light (Box 3, Item 1171)
  - Increase of Crime (Box 3, Item 1172)
  - Indian Hunter (Box 3, Item 1173)
  - Irish Molly, O! (Box 3, Item 1174)
  - Irish Spree (Box 3, Item 1175)
  - Irish Volunteer (Box 3, Item 1176)
  - Irish Volunteer (Box 3, Item 1177)
  - Irishman's Shanty (Box 3, Item 1178)
  - Irishman's Toast (Box 3, Item 1179)
  - In the Gloaming (Box 3, Item 1180)
  - Is Marriage a Failure? (Box 3, Item 1181)
  - Just As Of Old (Box 3, Item 1182)
  - Market on Saturday Night (Box 3, Item 1183)
  - Marseilles Hymn (Box 3, Item 1184)
  - Mary Ann Kehoe (Box 3, Item 1185)
  - McCarthy's Mare (Box 3, Item 1186)
  - Meet Me at the Lane (Box 3, Item 1187)
  - Flora May (Box 3, Item 1188)
  - Meet Me By Moonlight Willie (Box 3, Item 1189)
  - Minute Gun At Sea (Box 3, Item 1190)
  - Moon Is Beaming O'er the Lake (Box 3, Item 1191)
  - The Mother's Reply to "Rock Me to Sleep" (Box 3, Item 1192)
  - The Mountain Bugle (Box 3, Item 1193)
  - Muldoon the Solid Man (Box 3, Item 1194)
  - My Maryland (Box 3, Item 1195)
  - New Johnny, Fill up the Bowl! (Box 3, Item 1196)
  - The New-York Fire-Zouaves (Box 3, Item 1197)
  - No Irish Need Apply (Box 3, Item 1198)
  - Noble Knights of Labor (Box 3, Item 1199)
  - Noble Lads of Brooklyn (Box 3, Item 1200)
  - The Officer's Funeral (Box 3, Item 1201)
  - The Officer's Funeral (Box 3, Item 1202)
  - The Old Union Wagon (Box 3, Item 1203)
  - Our Country's Flag (Box 3, Item 1204)
  - Our Flag's Come Back to Tennessee (Box 3, Item 1205)
  - Our Gallant Colonel (Box 3, Item 1206)
  - Our Gallant Colonel (Box 3, Item 1207)
  - Our Good Ship Sails To-night (Box 3, Item 1208)
  - Our Heroes (Box 3, Item 1209)
  - Our Native Land (Box 3, Item 1210)
  - Our Native Land! (Box 3, Item 1211)
  - Our Torn Flag (Box 3, Item 1212)
  - Our Union, Right or Wrong (Box 3, Item 1213)
  - Our Union, Right or Wrong (Box 3, Item 1214)
  - Our Yankee Generals (Box 3, Item 1215)
  - Our Yankee Generals (Box 3, Item 1216)
  - Stars and Stripes No. 2 (Box 3, Item 1217)
  - Stove-Pipe Volunteers (Box 3, Item 1218)
  - Take Back the Heart (Box 3, Item 1219)
  - Take Back the Heart (Box 3, Item 1220)
  - Quite English, You Know (Box 3, Item 1221)
  - Quite English, You Know (Box 3, Item 1222)
  - Quiet Lodgings (Box 3, Item 1223)
  - The Song of All Songs (Box 3, Item 1224)
  - The Song of All Songs No. 2 (Box 3, Item 1225)
  - Song of All Songs No. 3 (Box 3, Item 1226)
  - Song of the First of Arkansas (Box 3, Item 1227)
  - Song of the Privateer (Box 3, Item 1228)
  - Le Soupir des Esclaves (Box 3, Item 1229)
  - Stars & Stripes (Box 3, Item 1230)
  - Take Back the Heart (Box 3, Item 1231)
  - Take Care of Number One (Box 3, Item 1232)
  - Taking It Cool (Box 3, Item 1233)
  - The Tax Bill (Box 3, Item 1234)
  - The Temple Fire (Box 3, Item 1235)
  - The Tenth, Montgomery Regiment (Box 3, Item 1236)
  - That Southern Wagon (Box 3, Item 1237)
  - That's Just So! (Box 3, Item 1238)
  - That's What's the Matter (Box 3, Item 1239)
  - That's Where the Laugh Comes In! (Box 3, Item 1240)
  - Ballad No. 2. Their Trophies (Box 3, Item 1241)
  - Then the Band Played (Box 3, Item 1242)
  - There Never Was a Coward Where the Shamrock Grows (Box 3, Item 1243)
  - There Never Was a Coward Where the Shamrock Grows (Box 3, Item 1244)
  - They Have Broken Up Their Camps! (Box 3, Item 1245)
  - They Never Told a Lie (Box 3, Item 1246)
  - Those Stripes and Bright Stars! (Box 3, Item 1247)
  - Thou Art So Near and Yet So Far (Box 3, Item 1248)
  - Faces (Box 3, Item 1249)
  - Throw Him Down McCloskey (Box 3, Item 1250)
  - Tim Finigan's Wake (Box 3, Item 1251)
  - Ting! Ting! That's How the Bell Goes (Box 3, Item 1252)
  - Tis Sad to Leave Your Fatherland (Box 3, Item 1253)
  - To a Brother Fighting for the Union (Box 3, Item 1254)
  - To Show my Respects to McGinnis (Box 3, Item 1255)
  - To the Happy Land of Union (Box 3, Item 1256)
  - Tom Bowling (Box 3, Item 1257)
  - Tommy, Do It Again (Box 3, Item 1258)
  - The Toper's Lament (Box 3, Item 1259)
  - Traitor, Spare that Flag! (Box 3, Item 1260)
  - Traitor, Spare that Flag (Box 3, Item 1261)
  - Traitor's March to the White-House! (Box 3, Item 1262)
  - Traitors Played Out. The Traitor's Doom (Box 3, Item 1263)
  - The True Jersey Blue (Box 3, Item 1264)
  - Turn Down Your Collar (Box 3, Item 1265)
  - Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Stars (Box 3, Item 1266)
  - The Two Pickets (Box 3, Item 1267)
  - Up Comes McGinty (Box 3, Item 1268)
  - Up in a Back Room (Box 3, Item 1269)
  - Uncle Billy's Dream (Box 3, Item 1270)
  - Uncle Ned (Box 3, Item 1271)
  - Warren's Address (Box 3, Item 1272)
  - When Johnny Comes Marching Home (Box 3, Item 1273)
  - When Johnny Comes Marching Home (Box 3, Item 1274)
  - When the Boys Come Home (Box 3, Item 1275)
  - When the Boys Come Marching Home (Box 3, Item 1276)
  - When This Cruel Draft Is Over! (Box 3, Item 1277)
  - When This Cruel War Is Over (Box 3, Item 1278)
  - Where Liberty Dwells, There Is My Country (Box 3, Item 1279)
  - Where Liberty Dwells, There Is My Country (Box 3, Item 1280)
  - Where Will I Go When Dis War Breaks Dis Country Up (Box 3, Item 1281)
  - Where's That Back Pay? (Box 3, Item 1282)
  - The White House (Box 3, Item 1283)
  - White Star Division (Box 3, Item 1284)
  - White Stars! (Box 3, Item 1285)
  - Who Can Find Us Now? (Box 3, Item 1286)
  - Who Will Care for Mickey Now? (Box 3, Item 1287)
  - Who Will Care for Mother Now? (Box 3, Item 1288)
  - Who Will Care for Mother Now? (Box 3, Item 1289)
  - Who Will Care for niggers now? (Box 3, Item 1290)
  - Who Will Care for Old Abe Now? (Box 3, Item 1291)
  - Who'll Have Me Now? (Box 3, Item 1292)
  - The Wide-Awakes (Box 3, Item 1293)
  - Wide-Awakes (Box 3, Item 1294)
  - The Widow's Last Prayer (Box 3, Item 1295)
  - Will They Weep For Me At Home? (Box 3, Item 1296)
  - Willie Has Gone to the War (Box 3, Item 1297)
  - With a Helmet on his Brow (Box 3, Item 1298)
  - Wont We Be a Happy People When This War Is Over (Box 3, Item 1299)
  - Wont We Be a Happy People When This War Is Over (Box 3, Item 1300)
  - A Wounded Soldier to his Comrades (Box 3, Item 1301)
  - Written for Rebecca (Box 3, Item 1302)
  - Yankee Boys, So Handy, O! (Box 3, Item 1303)
  - Yankee Boys, So Handy, O! (Box 3, Item 1304)
  - Yankee Boys So Handy O! (Box 3, Item 1305)
  - Yankee Doodle (Box 3, Item 1306)
  - Yankee Doodle (Box 3, Item 1307)
  - Yankee Doodle. No. 3 (Box 3, Item 1308)
  - Yankee Doodle Uncle Sam (Box 3, Item 1309)
  - Yankee Volunteer (Box 3, Item 1310)
  - Yan-kee-dom! (Box 3, Item 1311)
  - Young America and Ould Ireland (Box 3, Item 1312)
  - The Young Conscript and his Lady (Box 3, Item 1313)
  - Young Eph's Lament (Box 3, Item 1314)
  - Young Eph's Lament (Box 3, Item 1315)
  - The Young Invincible (Box 3, Item 1316)
  - Young Recruit (Box 3, Item 1317)
  - Zarvona (Box 3, Item 1318)
  - Kind Friends Are Near Her (Box 3, Item 1319)
  - Kingdom Coming (Box 3, Item 1320)
  - Kingdom Coming (Box 3, Item 1321)
  - Kitty Wells (Box 3, Item 1322)
  - Keystone Brigade (Box 3, Item 1323)
  - The Last of the 'Alabama' (Box 3, Item 1324)
  - "The Last Ditch!" (Box 3, Item 1325)
  - Liberty-All Hail (Box 3, Item 1326)
  - Liberty Tree (Box 3, Item 1327)
  - Liberty Tree (Box 3, Item 1328)
  - Liberty Tree (Box 3, Item 1329)
  - Lilly and her Soldier (Box 3, Item 1330)
  - Lookout Mountain (Box 3, Item 1331)
  - Look Out! The Rebels are Coming (Box 3, Item 1332)
  - Lone Star (Box 3, Item 1333)
  - Long Live McClellan! (Box 3, Item 1334)
  - Long Live the Sixty-Ninth (Box 3, Item 1335)
  - Long Live the Sixty-Ninth! (Box 3, Item 1336)
  - Love Thee (Box 3, Item 1337)
  - Lovely Dolly Day (Box 3, Item 1338)
  - Louey Napoleon (Box 3, Item 1339)
  - Poor Black Bess (Box 3, Item 1340a)
  - Lula is Gone (Box 3, Item 1340b)
  - Parody On Dear Mother, I've Come Home to Die (Box 3, Item 1341)
  - Parody On Mother, I've Come Home to Die (Box 3, Item 1342)
  - Parody On When This Cruel War Is Over (Box 3, Item 1343)
  - Parody On When This Cruel War Is Over (Box 3, Item 1344)
  - The Pass of Death (Box 3, Item 1345)
  - Pat Murphy of Meagher's Brigade (Box 3, Item 1346)
  - The Patriotic Contraband! (Box 3, Item 1347)
  - The Patriot's Call to Duty (Box 3, Item 1348)
  - The Peanut Stand (Box 3, Item 1349)
  - The Pennsylvanian Battle Cry (Box 3, Item 1350)
  - The Pennsylvanian Battle Cry! (Box 3, Item 1351)
  - The Pennsylvania Volunteers (Box 3, Item 1352)
  - Philadelphia Riots (Box 3, Item 1353a)
  - Whig Songs (Box 3, Item 1353b)
  - Physic for Traitors! (Box 3, Item 1354)
  - The Picket Guard (Box 3, Item 1355)
  - Picket's Last Watch (Box 3, Item 1356)
  - The Pig Is Greased Behind (Box 3, Item 1357)
  - Pirate's Chorus (Box 3, Item 1358)
  - Pompey Moore (Box 3, Item 1359)
  - Pity the Sorrows of a Poor Old Man (Box 3, Item 1360)
  - Prayer During Battle (Box 3, Item 1361)
  - Prayer for our Country (Box 3, Item 1362)
  - The President's Ball (Box 3, Item 1363)
  - President's Ball (Box 3, Item 1364)
  - The Prisoner's Plea (Box 3, Item 1365)
  - The Prisoner's Release (Box 3, Item 1366)
  - Proud Columbia (Box 3, Item 1367)
  - The Rebel Ram (Box 3, Item 1368)
  - Rebel, Spare that Flag! (Box 3, Item 1369)
  - Red Hot (Box 3, Item 1370)
  - Red, White & Blue! (Box 3, Item 1371)
  - Red, White and Blue (Box 3, Item 1372)
  - Relief for Ireland (Box 3, Item 1373)
  - Remember Baltimore (Box 3, Item 1374)
  - Return of Gen. Corcoran of the Glorious 69th (Box 3, Item 1375)
  - Rhode Island Volunteer (Box 3, Item 1376)
  - Richmond Jail (Box 3, Item 1377)
  - Robin Adair (Box 3, Item 1378)
  - Rock of Liberty (Box 3, Item 1379)
  - Root Hog or Die (Box 3, Item 1380)
  - Rosalie! The Prarie Flower (Box 3, Item 1381)
  - The Bummer's Hope (Box 3, Item 1382)
  - Striking Ile (Box 3, Item 1383)
  - The Sword and the Red, White and Blue (Box 3, Item 1384)
  - Sword of Bunker Hill! (Box 3, Item 1385)
  - Uncle Ned (Box 3, Item 1386)
  - Uncle Sam's Boys (Box 3, Item 1387)
  - Under the Daisies! (Box 3, Item 1388)
  - Under the Willow She's Sleeping (Box 3, Item 1389)
  - Up Comes McGinty (Box 3, Item 1390)
  - Up in a Back Room (Box 3, Item 1391)
  - Upper Ten and the Lower Five (Box 3, Item 1392)
  - Veteran (Box 3, Item 1393)
  - Volunteers' Song (Box 3, Item 1394)
  - Wake Nicodemus! (Box 3, Item 1395)
  - Wanderer (Box 3, Item 1396)
  - We Are Coming Sister Mary (Box 3, Item 1397)
  - What is Home Without a Mother? (Box 3, Item 1398)
  - When My Ship Comes In (Box 3, Item 1399)
  - When You've Got Money (Box 3, Item 1400)
  - Where Did You Get That Hat (Box 3, Item 1401)
  - Where Is Major Phipps? (Box 3, Item 1402)
  - White Wings (Box 3, Item 1403)
  - The Wife's Dream (Box 3, Item 1404)
  - Yaller Gal that Winked at Me (Box 3, Item 1405)
  - Yankee Ship and Yankee Crew (Box 3, Item 1406)
  - You Get More Like Your Dad Every Day (Box 3, Item 1407)
  - Young Man from the Country (Box 3, Item 1408)
  - The Soldier's Farewell to his Bride (Box 3, Item 1409)
  - Hark! The Summons (Box 3, Item 1410)
  - Southern Sentiments (Box 3, Item 1411)
  - Monument, at Lowell (Box 3, Item 1412)
  - The New Dixie (Box 3, Item 1413)
  - Marvin (Box 3, Item 1414)
  - "Quamdiu tandem abutere patientiae nostra?" (Box 3, Item 1415)
  - A Prayer to be Said by All Good Citizens on the Day of Fasting & Prayer (Box 3, Item 1416)
  - Battle Hymn of the Republic (Box 3, Item 1417)
  - Bull's Run (Box 3, Item 1418)
  - Oh! Abraham, Resign! (Box 3, Item 1419)
  - Ode for the One Hundred and Fiftieth Anniversary of the South Carolina Society (Box 3, Item 1420)
  - Jackson is Dead! (Box 3, Item 1421)
  - Stonewall Jackson's Way (Box 3, Item 1422)
  - Maryland (Box 3, Item 1423)
  - There's Life in the Old Land Yet (Box 3, Item 1424)
  - Old Folks at Home (Box 3, Item 1425a)
  - Massa's in the Cold Ground (Box 3, Item 1425b)
  - Marching Along No. 2 (Box 3, Item 1426)
  - When This Cruel War is Over (Box 3, Item 1427)
  - Will You Love Me Then as Now (Box 3, Item 1428)
  - The Glorious 69th (Box 3, Item 1429)
  - Erin's Lovely Home (Box 3, Item 1430)
  - Doran's Ass (Box 3, Item 1431)
  - Joe Hooker's Official Dispatch (Box 3, Item 1432)
  - Bless the Lord, O My (Box 3, Item 1433)
  - The Battle of Cedar Creek (Box 3, Item 1434)
  - Mott Street, 449 (Box 3, Item 1435)
  - Hush, My Darlings, Do Not Weep (Box 3, Item 1436)
  - Good-Bye, Sweetheart (Box 3, Item 1437)
  - Little Brown Jug (Box 3, Item 1438)
  - The Battle of Cedar Creek (Box 3, Item 1439)
  - The Battle of Cedar Creek (Box 3, Item 1440)
  - Brave Boys Are They (Box 3, Item 1441)
  - How the Veterans Broke Up Jeff Davis' Ball (Box 3, Item 1442)